expedino.com 2015-04-07

# Privacy Policy : Expedino.Com

## Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy for _expedino.com_  
**Your Privacy**  
Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

**Cookies**  
While browsing _expedino.com_ , a small number of text files referred to as “cookies” may be created on your local file system by your web browser at the request of our servers. These files allow us to personalize the browsing experience for both registered and non-registered users. You are free to delete them at any time, or configure your browser not to create them. However, we do not promise that every feature of _expedino.com_ will function as expected without cookies enabled.

**Collection of Personal Information**  
when visiting _expedino.com_ , the IP address used to access the site will be logged along with the dates and times of access. This information is purely used to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement and gather broad demographic information for internal use. Most importantly, any recorded IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.

**Third-Party Advertisers**  
In order to cover the costs of providing Imagesci.com as a free resource to the public, we have relationships with many third-party advertising networks. The practices of our advertising partners are not directly covered by _expedino.com_ privacy policy. We recommend that you read their policies. For your convenience we provide a list our advertising partners below. Unfortunately we cannot guarantee it is always comprehensive and up to date.

**Google Adsense:**  
We present you the following information about Google and the DoubleClick DART cookie:  
Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.

Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.  
For any problems or questions don’t hesitate to **Contact Us**.
